[
    {
        "Question":"Nmap argument for 'no port scan'.",
        "Answer":["-sP","-sn"]
    },
    {
        "Question":"Nmap argument for providing more debug information about sending packets.",
        "Answer":["--packet-trace"]
    },
    {
        "Question":"Nmap argument to disable ARP discovery packet to be utilized.",
        "Answer":["--disable-arp-ping","-send-ip"]
    },
    {
        "Question":"Nmap argument for TCP SYN Ping Scan.",
        "Answer":["-PS"]
    },
    {
        "Question":"Nmap argument for ACK Ping Scan.",
        "Answer":["-PA"]
    },
    {
        "Question":"Nmap argument for ICMP Echo Ping Scan.",
        "Answer":["-PE"]
    },
    {
        "Question":"Nmap argument for ICMP Address Mask Scan.",
        "Answer":["-PM"]
    },
    {
        "Question":"Nmap argument for ICMP Echo Timestamp Scan.",
        "Answer":["-PP"]
    },
    {
        "Question":"Nmap for UDP Ping Scan.",
        "Answer":["-PU"]
    },
    {
        "Question":"Nmap argument for IP Ping Scan.",
        "Answer":["-PO"]
    },
    {
        "Question":"Nmap argument for ARP Scan.",
        "Answer":["-PR"]
    },
    {
        "Question":"Nmap argument for SCTP INIT Ping Scan",
        "Answer":["-PY"]
    },
    {
        "Question":"Nmap argument for traceroute",
        "Answer":["--traceroute"]
    }
]